[Music]
[Música]
We did things incredibly well and they
dimos las cosas increíblemente bien y
would have continued to go well but what
habrían segido saliendo bien pero qué
happened they used the the other day I got into the
pasó usaron los el otro día me metí al
Best col live And how disgusting it is going
directo de Best col Y qué asco va de
high The kid has to learn to
subidito El chaval tiene que aprender a
respect the ranks damn Botero gey they
respetar los rangos [__] Botero gey me
have it in for me for having exposed them I
tienen ganas por haberlos expuesto Yo
previously for being scammers
anteriormente por ser unos estafadores
some Defenders of like Sprint for
unos Defensores de como Sprint por
example Sprint started doing this and
ejemplo Sprint se puso a hacer esto y
why are you burned by me Because I
por qué tees ardido conmigo Porque te
humiliated you because I exposed you for being aig of
humill porque te expuse por ser aig de
a because I exposed you now you try to
un porque te expuse ahora intentas
pretend that I am the bad one I did
fingir que yo soy el malo yo hecho las
things right and I will die on the last day of
cosas bien y moriré el el último día de
my days I will die knowing that I did
mis días moriré sabiendo que hice las
things right and I will always know it all these
cosas bien y lo sabré siempre toda esta
people will die knowing that their life was
gentuza morirán sabiendo que su vida fue
one always that it was always one I believe
una siempre que siempre fue una yo creo
that this man someday the news will come out
que este señor algún día saldrán las
and they will say Dallas review has
noticias y dirán Dallas review ha
murdered his wife LICP he has killed
asesinado a su mujer licp ha matado a
four children in the street and you have
cuatro niños por la calle y me has
stolen all my money but I love you d
robado todo mi dinero pero te amo d
condemn Coscu Guayayaya was
condenen a coscu guayayayaya ha
found hanged in  a forest I
encontrado ahorcado en un bosque te lo
swear eh Ed say right now I would bet
juro eh Ed diro ahora mismo apostaría
there is more chance of that that Pambi
hay más chances de eso de que pambi
will rise again seriously eh sir It's not
vuelva a subir en serio eh seor No está
good no no it's good but it's not good
bien no no está bien pero no está bien
but it's not even close to being good what a
pero no está ni cerca de estar bien qué
barbarity he is completely crazy yes yes he
barbaridad está completamente ido sí sí
is a katanas he is the katana killer he
es un katanas es el asesino de la catana
is a [ __ ] katanas this one
es un [__] catanas a este algún día
comes here one day with a [ __ ] katana to
viene aquí con una [__] katana a
chase children through the middle of
perseguir niños por el medio de la
Merich Avenue in Andorra you know what
avenida merich de andorra sabes qué
madness man it's getting out of hand well no
locura tío se le va de las manos buen no
because in Andorra I think they don't let him
porque en andorra creo que no le dejan
live because he has a criminal record
vivir porque tiene antecedentes penales
So they kicked him out like that I don't think
Así que lo echaron así que ya no creo
he's in Andorra anymore that in Dallas they don't
que esté en andorra que en Dallas no le
let him live in Andorra because he
que en andorra no le dejan vivir porque
has a criminal record Don't [ __ ] with something like that
tiene antecedentes penales No jodas algo
Something like that I know that Andorra can't
así Algo así s que andorra no puede
be what criminal record does
estar qué antecedentes penales tiene el
Dallas have come on no we would not have
Dallas vamos no no nos hubiéramos
found out if they had sentenced him to
enterado de que lo hubieran condenado a
something criminal I don't know why
algo penal no lo sé por eso
but I'm almost sure that in Andorra he
pero estoy casi segura que en andorra no
is not but the thing is that in Andorra it is very
no está pero es que en andorra es muy
important not to have a criminal record or to
importante el no tener antecedentes ni
have any trial or any open criminal case
tener ningún juicio ni ningún caso penal
or  nothing like that And he's up
abierto ni nada por el estilo Y está
to his neck in absolutely
metido hasta el cuello en absolutamente
everything You know So G let's play
todo Sabes Así que G vamos ayar un
LoL a little bit, let's go up to Challenger,
poquito al LoL vamos subir a Challenger
Kick's PP is disgusting Really what a
es asquerosa la PP de Kick De verdad qué
madness you look for the profile and the live doesn't open or
locura buscas el perfil y no abre el
info or anything comes up Javi's tet
directo ni sale info ni nada tet de Javi
for you pass it to him I'm missing Out of
para ti páselo a le estoy faltando Sin
Control to Dalas you know but it's funny
Control a Dalas sabes pero es divertido
this type must be based on
de este tipo deben basarse en pruebas
conas tests and in many cases Oh okay I mean
conas y en muchos casos Ah vale o sea
but this gave him a like look you see it the
pero esto le dio like mira lo ves está
like is instant What was the tweet
el like al instante Cuál ha sido el twit
for which he whistled What is the tweet
por el que se ha pitado Cuál es el tweet
for which he got so pissed off then
por el que se ha picado tanto entonces
ciado hahaha He is one of the most
ciado jajaja Es de los seres más
[ __ ] beings that can exist these people
retrasados que pueden existir esta gente
are very Low iq what an idiot the millo
es muy Low iq qué idiota el millo
needs an AI to explain to him
necesita una ia para que le expliquen
about a scam I need an AI to
sobre una estafa Necesito una ia para
explain to me about anything not
que me expliqu sobre cualquier cosa no
the best way to inform yourself of
la mejor forma de informarte de la
most situations in this this 2024
mayoría de situaciones en este este 2024
not in your day to day I use it Every day
no en tu día a día lo utilizo Cada día
I well these people go go
yo pues esta esta gente va va
literally justify the
literalmente justificar lo
unjustifiable it is not to say literally there is  there
injustificable no es decir literalmente
is evidence where Dallas has
hay hay pruebas donde donde Dallas ha
sold a large percentage of the
vendido un porcentaje grande de de la
currency to steal money from viewers
moneda para robarle dinero a los viewers
No now the friend's wallet has come out
No ahora ha salido la cartera del colega
at this moment that this if I'm not
en este momento que esto si no me
mistaken is the day before yesterday I think it's at the same
equivoco es antes de ayer creo que es a
time that I posted the tweet no because it is
la vez que puse el tweet no porque está
reacting to the tweet eh there was not
reacionando al tweet eh ahí no había ni
even confirmation that anyone on the
siquiera confirmación de que nadie del
team had a sale They were
equipo tuviera una venta Eran
all speculations where you can see that he
especulaciones todas donde se ve que
has several wallets where ryo evidence
tiene varias carteras donde ryo pruebas
What evidence do you want to be literally
Qué pruebas quieres estar literalmente
in the blockchain because the guy is so
en la blockchain porque el tío está tan
low iq that he is not even capable of hiding it like you
low iq que no es capaz ni de ocultarlo
see someone on a
en plan ves a alguien en una cámara de
security camera who kills another person and
seguridad que mata a otra persona y te
Javi L comes to you and says no no but you
viene Javi L y dice no no pero lo has
saw it with your own eyes because the
visto con tus propios ojos porque la
security camera maybe crazy just slit
cámara de seguridad quizá loco acaba de
someone's throat in front of the
degollar a una persona delante de la
[ __ ] security camera and you could
[__] cámara de seguridad y se le ha
see his face is that no no he didn't say he did
visto la cara es que no no ha dicho que
n't say his name maybe it was someone
no ha dicho su nombre quizá era alguien
who looked a lot like crazy it is it is It's
que se parecía mucho loco es es Es
Andorra has slit someone's throat you can
andorra ha Degollado una persona se le
see his face oh no but but maybe he has
ve la cara ah no pero pero quizá tiene
a twin brother Dallas Well I don't
un hermano gemelo Dallas Bueno yo queé
know like go and eat his dick  more is that
sé en plan ve y com la [__] más es que
what a [ __ ] outrage like they would
qué [__] barbaridad en plan
justify the unjustifiable it is an
justificarían lo injustificable es una
outrage What madness eh or already he has
barbaridad Qué locura eh o ya está ha
caught 300 or 400,000 Nothing happens It is
escamado 300 o 400,000 No pasa nada Es
strange not that you want to exchange 300 or 400,000
raro no que quieras es cambar 300 o
when he had recently donated
400,000 cuando hace poco le había donado
10 million But well there is also
10 millones Pero bueno también hay
evidence for coscu and you did not
pruebas para lo de coscu y no lo
condemn him there is no evidence of ccu
condenaste no hay pruebas de de ccu
no man you like ccu the best you like
no tío te gusta ccu el millor te gusta
cocu man you would have liked the
el cocu tío te hubiera gustado que la
photo to be with you or what is going on
foto fuera contigo o qué es lo que pasa
my god there is no evidence for ccu
madre mía no hay pruebas para lo de ccu
says the
dice el
note I mean what comes out of his dick
nota o sea de lo que le sale de la [__]
what comes out of his dick that there is that there is
de lo que le sale de la [__] eso hay
tremendous evidence eh that well
eso hay tremendas pruebas eh eso bueno
that is impossible irrefutable okay And it is
eso es imposible irrefutable vale Y está
super proven But well well wello as
super probado Pero bueno bueno buenoo de
for kku there is no evidence whatsoever Eh there is
lo de kku no hay prueba ninguna Eh hay
evidence of kcu of absolutely
pruebas de lo de kcu de absolutamente
nothing besides I know coscu in
nada además que yo conozco a coscu en
person and conco Ah okay besides I
persona y conco Ah vale además que yo lo
know him in person So there can be no
conozco en persona Entonces no puede
evidence of course I am that  I do
haber pruebas claro Yo es que al dasas
n't know al dasas in person. I know what is
no lo conozco en persona conozco Cuál es
the situation of an influencer of his of
la situación de de un influencer de de
his size like no I would never ever
su de su tamaño en plan no nunca jamás
condemn something like that it is complete
condenaría algo así es una completa
stupidity It is simply stupid the
estupidez Es simplemente estúpido la
photo is not proof of the Rafle password
foto no es prueba contraseña de la rafle
immortality I don't know They are different moral things The
inmortalidad no sé Son son cosas Morales
thing about the photo is something that is
diferentes Lo de la foto es algo que que
good sicu decides to share that photo with
bueno sicu decide compartir esa foto con
a friend of his, let him do it if the girl
un amigo suyo que lo haga si la chica
agrees with it, well if the
está de acuerdo con ello bien si la
girl does not agree with it, let him
chica no está de acuerdo con ello que lo
report it, period like it is already like
denuncie punto en plan es que ya está en
the girl did not report him like
plan la chica no lo denunció en plan
everything is fine between cosco and the girl, well that's it I
está todo bien entre cosco y la chica
mean I don't see
pues ya está es decir no veo
absolutely any problem anymore you
absolutamente ningún problema má no
can't be eh judges of these things
podéis ser eh jueces de estas cosas
you know like judges it can only be
sabes en plan jueces solamente puede ser
him who the [ __ ] are you to say about a
él quién [__] sois para decir de una
photo that ccu sent to a friend 10
foto que ccu mandó a un amigo hace 10
years ago that he is going crazy it didn't make
años que que se va de la cabeza no tenía
any [ __ ] sense it doesn't make any [ __ ]
ningún [__] sentido no tiene ningún [__]
sense plan they try to accuse
sentido plan se le intenta atachar a
coscu of being a rapist when the guy slept
coscu de violador cuando el tío Se tiró
with a girl you know like or that's it or he
a una chavala sabes en plan o ya está o
slept or whatever  be like What the
durmió o lo que sea en plan What the
[ __ ] who the [ __ ] a drunk girl was really really
fuck quién [__] una chavala borracha muy
drunk and took a picture of him while he was
muy borracha y le hizo una foto estando
unconscious and then sent it around
inconsciente que luego la mandó por ahí
words from him he has not had sex while
palabras de él no ha tenido sexo estando
drunk like who hasn't had that
borracho en plan quién no ha tenido que
to this day it's impressive it's that he
a día de hoy es impresionante es que
had sex with a drunk girl I've
tuvo sexo con una chavala borracha yo he
had sex with drunk girls
tenido sexo con chavalas borrachas
countless times always
incontables e innumerables veces siempre
consensual But well I mean if I'm
consentido Pero bueno me refiero si yo
drunk the other girl is drunk and all
voy borracho la otra cha borracha y tal
And we have sex we have sex But you
Y tenemos sexo tenemos sexo Pero tú le
took pictures of her and sent them
has hecho fotos y las has mandado por
around without consent what what what the most
ahí sin consentimiento qu qué qué lo más
normal thing in the world dude this thing has nothing to
normal del mundo tío no tiene nada que
do with coscu with Dallas Dallas there is
ver lo de coscu con Dallas Dallas hay
literally evidence where the guy has
literalmente pruebas donde el tío ha
scammed hundreds of thousands of euros
escamado cientos de miles de euros
hundreds of thousands of euros well
cientos de miles de euros pues ya me
you tell me how the hell you scammed hundreds
dirás tú comoo [__] has escado cientos
of thousands of euros with what was in the
de miles de euros con lo que había en la
pool from his followers abusing how low
pool a sus seguidores abusando de lo low
IQ they are Because if they are
iq que son Porque si son suficientemente
low IQ enough to believe the nonsense
low iq como para creerle las tonterías
in the videos he always makes they will also
de videos que hace siempre también lo
do it to give him the money and
van a hacer para regalarle el dinero e
as for coscu there is absolutely not a
lo de coscu no hay absolutamente ni una
single proof or there is  absolutely nothing like anyone who
sola prueba ni hay absolutamente nada en
can say something to you is that as a
pueda decir algo es que por Norma
general rule it's an idiot you are in a
general Es imbécil estáis en un estado
similar state of drunkenness it's okay you know if
de ebriedad parecido está bien sabes si
the other person wants it and you want it
la otra persona quiere y tú quieres Está
Okay there's absolutely no
bien no hay absolutamente ningún
problem and this already today don't put it I have
problema y esto ya hoy no ponas lo tengo
threatened to take his children that's why he
amenazado con llevarme a sus hijos por
defends me guajaja chat Of course
eso me defiende guajaja chat Claro que
tomorrow I'm not going to do the same thing when I
mañana no voy a hacer lo mismo cuando he
said something and I haven't followed through
dicho algo y no lo he cumplido
guaja you Far Shut the [ __ ] up Shut the
guaja tu Far Shut the fuck up Shut the
[ __ ] up eat my [ __ ] the old man of the
fuck up me coma la [__] el viejo de los
balls don't lower yourself funny funny I didn't
[__] no te rebajes gracioso gracioso
say anything don't bring the daughters together
no he dicho nada no metas a las hijas
for God what else at what point did I
por Dios qué más en qué momento he
put my son I said if the daughters are
metido hij he dicho que si las hijas le
going to see him in jail at what
van a ir a ver a la cárcel en qué
point did I say something about the daughters
momento he dicho algo de las hijas
normal don't ask like if they
normal no preguntar en plan e si te
put your family in jail Will they go to
meten a la cárcel tu familia Te ira a
see you in jail or not want a
ver a la cárcel o no quies una pregunta
normal question I hope I have the same luck
normal espero tener la misma suerte que
you had when Cristin reported you
tuviste tú cuando te denunció cristin
Cristin has never reported me She
cristin no me ha denunciado nunca no me
has never reported me a normal question I
ha denunciado nunca una pregunta normal
hope I have the same luck you had
espero tener la misma suerte que tuviste
you when cristin reported you cristin
tú cuando te denunció cristin cristin no
has never reported me Maybe this is a little
me ha denunciado nunca Quizás es un poco
lie
mentira
when she didn't report you Ah okay
esto cuando no te denunció Ah vale
Then what nonsense is that
Entonces qué tontería es esa
[Music]
[Música]
Oh What's the fling what's it like
Oh Cuál es el flameo cuál es en plan de
your ex hasn't reported you like my
tu ex a ti no te ha denunciado como a mi
friend Dallas who has been reported by all
amigo Dallas que le han denunciado todas
his ex-girlfriends
sus exnovias
Ah That's
Ah Ese es
the one that's the fling is that like W
el es es el flameo es ese en plan de W
well all his exes have reported him he
pues adas le han denunciado todas sus ex
already has
ya tiene
none he hasn't understood nor has he
ninguna no ha entendido ni no ha
understood the creature nor the tweet that nor
entendido la criatura ni ni el tweet que
the answer that I give him no the
ni la respuesta que yo le pongo no no la
creature hasn't understood it
ha entendido la criatura
right I'm sure I get along with all
verdad seguro me llevo bien con todas
my exes with Cris I get
mis ex con Cris me llevo
along like we had our ups and
bien en plan tuvimos nuestros más y
downs because we made the
nuestros menos porque hicimos la
public relationship and when he makes the
relación pública y cuando hace la
public relationship what there is but I
relación pública lo que hay pero yo me
get along with
llevo bien con
Cris [ __ ] supposedly he's a
Cris [__] supuestamente es un scammer
sectarian scammer No he's not a sectarian scammer he
sectario No no es un scammer sectario no
's not supposedly a sectarian scammer he's
es supuestamente un scammer sectario es
a sectarian scammer or what about
un scammer sectario o lo de
supposedly he has abused someone I
supuestamente ha abusado de alguien Yo
'm not saying that I mean yes yes
no estoy diciendo que me refiero si si
another person ASSUMES that he's a scammer
ot persona ASUME que es un scammer
sectarian I have not said
sectario yo no he dicho el nombre de
anyone's name here is some name of some
nadie aquí hay algún nombre de alguna
person here pisses if the other person
persona aquí meo si la otra persona se
identifies themselves as a sectarian scammer or
identifica como un scamer sectario o
Javi oliveira identifies another person
Javi oliveira identifica a otra persona
as their owner It's not my problem Eh yes or
como su dueño No es mi problema Eh sí o
no but I have not said anything specific but you
no per yo no he dicho nada concreto pero
identify another person as your owner I do
identificas a otra persona como tu dueño
n't know the other identifies himself as a
no sé el otro se identifica como un
sectarian scammer I don't [ __ ] know I do
scamer sectario I don't fucking know I
n't [ __ ] know little princess the only
don't fucking know princesita la única
reason why he doesn't even know her
razón por la que ni siquiera la conoce
is because she's showing her tits
es porque está enseñando las tetas en
everywhere you're right Mara Mara Who
todos lados tienes razón Mara Mara Quién
is mar when she is one of the most
es mar cuando es una de las personas más
limited and most righteous people that I've met
limitadas y más justitos que he conocido
in a long time I said that she's watching a
en mucho tiempo dije que está viendo un
video of mine now and why Chita has
vídeo mío ahora y por qué Chita tiene
more tits thanq let's see factor no factor no let's
más tetas queq a ver factor no factor no
see but this this It can only be
a ver pero esto lo esto Solo se puede
refuted in one way princess or so
rebatir de una forma princesita o sea
this It can only be refuted in one
esto Solamente se puede rebatir de una
way tes live without more it's
forma tes en directo sin más tiene su
funny Javier or beira this in plan
gracia el Javier o beira este en plan
has comments that are laughable it
tiene comentarios que dan risa pasa que
's a shame that he is a [ __ ] henchman
es una pena que que sea un [__] esbirro
of dalos he has a lot of companies
de dalos tiene un montón de compañías
that well lemon  Russian a kiss sweetheart There they are having
que bueno limon ruso un beso corazón Ahí
a fight with the best
están echándose un pulso con el millor
you guys who would you stay with the
ustedes con quién os quedaríais con el
best or with the Lan if they gave you the
millor o con el Lan si os dieran a
choice content creator that exists
elegir creador de contenido que existe
last content creator that exists
último creador de contenido que exist
you can choose you have to choose for balls
puedes eleg tienes que elegir por huev
also eh I mean you can't go watch
además eh o sea no puedes irte a ver
save me on TV you have to watch anu or
salvame a la tele tienes que ver anu o
the best I think the best eh I think I
el millor Yo creo que el millor eh creo
dislike an more eh look I
que me cae peor el an eh mira que el
dislike the best eh but not that bad I mean
millor me cae mal eh pero no tan mal o
with the best I could even have well
sea con el millor incluso Podría tener
come on you know it's that the nu
bueno venga va sabes es que la nu me
seems so Who is Teto bich and the
parece tan Quién es la Teto bich y el
pseudo Spaniard who are criticizing love
pseudo español que están criticando amar
my queen has told me that she has said it ca
a mi reina me ha dicho que me ha dicho
n't be no no it can't Have said it
no puede ser no no puede Haberlo dicho
no no she can't well yes she can
no no puede no puede pues si puede
best man It's that the one who seems so
millor tío Es que la que me parece tan
Who is tet Bach and the pseudo Spaniard
Quién es la tet Bach y el pseudo español
are criticizing love my queen isn't he
están criticando amar a mi reina no es
a little gay to be pending he said no it's that it
un poco gay llevar pendiente ha dicho no
's 3:45 in the morning and
es que son las 3:45 de la mañana y a lo
maybe I don't understand well czu's henchman  no no he doesn't
mejor yo no entiendo bien el esbirro de
make his intentions clear
czu no no me deja claras sus intenciones
he said he's a little gay wearing
ha dicho que es un poco gay llevar
earrings
pendientes
no no flame you know Not homophobic or anything like that
no no flame sabes No homofobo ni nada
but he's a little gay he's not
por el estilo pero es un poco gay no es
a little masculine the earrings without
poco masculino los pendientes sin
finding oh my god man but he
encontrar madre mía tío pero tanto te
blows your mind so much LoL man so much like
revienta la cabeza al LoL tío tantísimo
that he leaves you man do you see he's a little gay yes or
así te deja tío veis es un poco gay sí o
no Guillermo what do you think
no Guillermo qué opinas
you see a guy on the street and you're wearing
tú ves a un tío por la calle y llevas
these earrings and you think I can
estos pendientes y piensas le puedo
hit on him is he gay or punk one of two but if he
tirar es gay o cani una de dos pero si
's a little gay a little gay I think he did
es un poco gay un poco gay yo creo aquí
n't mention Dallas here okay This was at I's
no mencionó a Dallas vale Esto fue en la
house Who's going to mention Dallas like
casa de I Quién va a mencionar a Dallas
Javi In what world do you live nobody is going to
en plan Javi En qué mundo vives nadie va
mention Dallas because
a mencionar a Dallas porque todo el
everyone knows that everyone has a
mundo sabe que todo el mundo le tiene
crush on dasas like saying I watch
asco a dasas en plan decir el Yo veo los
millo's streams it could be eg it could be
streams del millo puede ser eg puede ser
different you could say Oh this person isn't
diferente puede decir Oh esta persona no
afraid but to say that with suum to
tiene miedo a pero decir que con suum a
Dallas is that you are mentally [ __ ]
Dallas es que eres [__] mental
You know I want to be crazy can you shut up already
Sabes quiero con loco puedes callarte ya
Javi oliveira you like to mess with
Javi oliveira tú me gusta meterme con
princess Ah I mean what is it to be a member
princesita Ah Es decir quees ser miembro
to talk now let's talk about that  now we
para hablar ahora hablamos de eso ahora
talk about that thing about how the earring is
hablamos de eso de qué el pendiente es
a little G the years go by that this This
un poco G pasan los años que que esto
is today This is when Look yes I
Esto es hoy Esto es cuando Mira sí que
am dressed this is today This is when I
estoy vestido esto es hoy Esto es cuando
wanted no no has become a member And what I
quería no no se ha hecho miembro Y qué
wanted to say and what about the millor he
quería decir y lo del millor me ha
sent me the millor But why am I going to have to
mandado del millor Pero por qué voy a
take action against the millor
tener que tomar medidas con el millor
for insulting us for saying a couple of
por insultarnos por decirnos un par de
bills publicly well now
billos públicamente bueno ahora
I will comment and see what it is that
comentaré y veré qué es lo que ha dicho
the millor has said okay But if it is because of the
el millor vale Pero si es por lo del
tweet yes what about the tweet It seems to me that it
twit si es que lo del twi Me parece que
leaves him worse than me it is that the
lo deja peor a él que mí es que lo del
tweet the tweet that he posted It seems to me
twit lo del twit que ha puesto Me parece
that it leaves him worse than me let's
que lo deja peor a él que a mí vamos a
see first let's put a squirrel
ver primero vamos a poner una ardilla
with everything that has happened because you
con todo lo que ha pasado porque me
are leaving me speechless How
estáis dejando de piedra Cómo ha
this has escalated Yesterday I was there I don't dislike him
escalado esto Ayer estuve no me cae mal
at all eh Javi Oliveira this one
del todo eh el Javi oliveira este en
like it pisses me off that he is so stupid of being
plan me jode que sea tan tonto de de ser
the Dallas dog but they take
el perro de Dallas pero se toman las
things with humor
cosas con humor
you know maybe it seems
sabes no s a lo mejor parece una
silly but for me for me it was
tontería pero para mí para mí fue un
completely a dream because I think that it
sueño completamente porque yo creo que
is  the only idol of mine That remains to be seen
es el único ídolo mío Que queda por ver
in person of those I can already see alive
en persona de los que ya puedo ver vivos
okay I already told you last week that
vale Ya os dije la semana pasada que
I had something incredible to do this
tenía yo algo increíble que hacer este
weekend and if then I and I
fin de semana y si luego yo con
agree on almost everything I don't agree on
coincidimos en casi todo no coincido en
anything with dasas on anything at all but on
nada con dasas en nada en nada pero en
nothing I don't give a [ __ ] Will Smith crazy
nada lo me suda la [__] Will Smith loco
Holy [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] everyone's a
Holy shit me suda [__] todo el mundo un
little gay there's not a guy I mean there isn't a
poco gay no hay un tío O sea no hay un
[ __ ] day that the best doesn't I mean
[__] día que el millor no me o sea
when I think I can't be surprised it
cuando creo que no me puede sorprender
always surprises me eh it
siempre me cae siempre me sorprende eh
always surprises me But anyway let's
siempre me sorprende Pero bueno vamos a
leave it Because look today at least he
dejarlo Porque mira hoy por lo menos ha
said that he doesn't like me that much so
dicho que no le caigo tan tan
[Music]
[Música]
badly i
mal i